[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "Can we say that for certain or could it be that there were some protesters and there was also a planned attack because it was September the 11th?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "say", "that", "for", "certain", "or", "could", "it", "be", "that", "there", "were", "some", "protesters", "and", "there", "was", "also", "a", "planned", "attack", "because", "it", "was", "September", "the", "11th", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["September"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Petraeus"]}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "But where do you position him in terms of his legacy as a general?", "question_tokens": ["But", "where", "do", "you", "position", "him", "in", "terms", "of", "his", "legacy", "as", "a", "general", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "One of the saddest aspects of this entire mess was that Petraeus was one of our best generals in recent years.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "of", "the", "saddest", "aspects", "of", "this", "entire", "mess", "was", "that", "Petraeus", "was", "one", "of", "our", "best", "generals", "in", "recent", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Was that your reading of it?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "your", "reading", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Yes, pretty much.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "pretty", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matthew Ridgway"]}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Where do you think General Petraeus ranks as a general, say, in the last hundred years?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "think", "General", "Petraeus", "ranks", "as", "a", "general", ",", "say", ",", "in", "the", "last", "hundred", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "I think he'll be remembered a lot like Matthew Ridgway, which is to say pretty much not at all except by the experts.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'ll", "be", "remembered", "a", "lot", "like", "Matthew", "Ridgway", ",", "which", "is", "to", "say", "pretty", "much", "not", "at", "all", "except", "by", "the", "experts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Petraeus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Paula"]}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "Did the Paula Broadwell book that came out about General Petraeus, did you like that as a historian?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "the", "Paula", "Broadwell", "book", "that", "came", "out", "about", "General", "Petraeus", ",", "did", "you", "like", "that", "as", "a", "historian", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "I -- I had introduced Paula, actually, to my book editor.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "had", "introduced", "Paula", ",", "actually", ",", "to", "my", "book", "editor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paula Broadwell", "Petraeus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "What I think is that spies are probably like soldiers.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "I", "think", "is", "that", "spies", "are", "probably", "like", "soldiers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hamas"]}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "NNP", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "How is this going to resolve itself?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "this", "going", "to", "resolve", "itself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "It's going to resolve itself when Hamas cease firing rockets at millions of innocent Israeli civilians.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "going", "to", "resolve", "itself", "when", "Hamas", "cease", "firing", "rockets", "at", "millions", "of", "innocent", "Israeli", "civilians", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Are you preparing for a ground invasion?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "preparing", "for", "a", "ground", "invasion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "We are certainly keeping that option open.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "are", "certainly", "keeping", "that", "option", "open", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "Would you like to live on the Gaza Strip?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "to", "live", "on", "the", "Gaza", "Strip", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "No, and I think the Gazans should make a decision about the type of government they want.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "and", "I", "think", "the", "Gazans", "should", "make", "a", "decision", "about", "the", "type", "of", "government", "they", "want", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Gaza Strip"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "The international community has got to somehow offer the people in Gaza more hope, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["The", "international", "community", "has", "got", "to", "somehow", "offer", "the", "people", "in", "Gaza", "more", "hope", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "RBR", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Well, the crossings have been open.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "crossings", "have", "been", "open", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Gaza"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "What did you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "Well, we preferred to look at Egyptian deeds rather than words.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "preferred", "to", "look", "at", "Egyptian", "deeds", "rather", "than", "words", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "Is your intention at the same time to continue targeting Hamas leaders and to continue, if you can, killing them?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "your", "intention", "at", "the", "same", "time", "to", "continue", "targeting", "Hamas", "leaders", "and", "to", "continue", ",", "if", "you", "can", ",", "killing", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "NNP", "NNS", "CC", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Well, we're going to take any measures necessary to stop the aggression against the civilians.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "take", "any", "measures", "necessary", "to", "stop", "the", "aggression", "against", "the", "civilians", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hamas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel", "Jerusalem"]}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "CC", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "What is the way to break through this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "way", "to", "break", "through", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "The way to break through it would be for the Palestinians to accept that there is a state of Israel, which is permanent and legitimate, and to sit down with us at the negotiating table to negotiate all the outstanding issues -- whether it'd be borders, refugees, Jerusalem, security, recognition.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "way", "to", "break", "through", "it", "would", "be", "for", "the", "Palestinians", "to", "accept", "that", "there", "is", "a", "state", "of", "Israel", ",", "which", "is", "permanent", "and", "legitimate", ",", "and", "to", "sit", "down", "with", "us", "at", "the", "negotiating", "table", "to", "negotiate", "all", "the", "outstanding", "issues", "--", "whether", "it", "'d", "be", "borders", ",", "refugees", ",", "Jerusalem", ",", "security", ",", "recognition", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "What is your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "That's not only disingenuous, but it's very misleading and it has very little to do with the truth.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "not", "only", "disingenuous", ",", "but", "it", "'s", "very", "misleading", "and", "it", "has", "very", "little", "to", "do", "with", "the", "truth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hamas"]}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "Does the PLO have any real control over Hamas?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "the", "PLO", "have", "any", "real", "control", "over", "Hamas", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "No, we don't have control over Hamas.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "have", "control", "over", "Hamas", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["PLO"], "LOCATION": ["Hamas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hamas"]}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "If you're an Israeli listening to this, it's saying, well, it's all very well you talking in about how to resolve this, but if you have no control whatsoever over the activities of Hamas, why should they trust you?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "'re", "an", "Israeli", "listening", "to", "this", ",", "it", "'s", "saying", ",", "well", ",", "it", "'s", "all", "very", "well", "you", "talking", "in", "about", "how", "to", "resolve", "this", ",", "but", "if", "you", "have", "no", "control", "whatsoever", "over", "the", "activities", "of", "Hamas", ",", "why", "should", "they", "trust", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "No, because Hamas did acknowledge that should there be a negotiated settlement that's accepted by a referendum, by the Palestinian people, then they are quite willing to abide by it.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "because", "Hamas", "did", "acknowledge", "that", "should", "there", "be", "a", "negotiated", "settlement", "that", "'s", "accepted", "by", "a", "referendum", ",", "by", "the", "Palestinian", "people", ",", "then", "they", "are", "quite", "willing", "to", "abide", "by", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hamas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "How do we get through the fact that both of them have pretty good arguments?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "we", "get", "through", "the", "fact", "that", "both", "of", "them", "have", "pretty", "good", "arguments", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Well, I think the danger is that they both escalate as a result.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "danger", "is", "that", "they", "both", "escalate", "as", "a", "result", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "From a military point of view, is there anything that the Americans could be doing or pushing the Israelis to do to try and somehow come to a resolution that can work?", "question_tokens": ["From", "a", "military", "point", "of", "view", ",", "is", "there", "anything", "that", "the", "Americans", "could", "be", "doing", "or", "pushing", "the", "Israelis", "to", "do", "to", "try", "and", "somehow", "come", "to", "a", "resolution", "that", "can", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NNPS", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Well, first of all, I think we have to accept that we're not going to kill our way to a solution here, that, in fact, in many cases the use of military force is counterproductive.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "think", "we", "have", "to", "accept", "that", "we", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "kill", "our", "way", "to", "a", "solution", "here", ",", "that", ",", "in", "fact", ",", "in", "many", "cases", "the", "use", "of", "military", "force", "is", "counterproductive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Who can bring that to them?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "can", "bring", "that", "to", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "Well, I agree with Alan that Israel certainly has a right to self-defense.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "agree", "with", "Alan", "that", "Israel", "certainly", "has", "a", "right", "to", "self-defense", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "RBR", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "Was that your reading?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "your", "reading", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Actually, in some ways, it made things more confusing.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", ",", "in", "some", "ways", ",", "it", "made", "things", "more", "confusing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "I mean, depending again who you talk to -- there you have a top general saying it's just gotten a lot muddier, and that actually -- is this the danger when you have the need to keep stuff classified because you're going after certain groups you think may have done this, but sending people out like Ambassador Rice to spin a yarn that it may have been a video protest?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "depending", "again", "who", "you", "talk", "to", "--", "there", "you", "have", "a", "top", "general", "saying", "it", "'s", "just", "gotten", "a", "lot", "muddier", ",", "and", "that", "actually", "--", "is", "this", "the", "danger", "when", "you", "have", "the", "need", "to", "keep", "stuff", "classified", "because", "you", "'re", "going", "after", "certain", "groups", "you", "think", "may", "have", "done", "this", ",", "but", "sending", "people", "out", "like", "Ambassador", "Rice", "to", "spin", "a", "yarn", "that", "it", "may", "have", "been", "a", "video", "protest", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ":", "EX", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "RB", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", ",", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "In some ways, I think Mark is right that it has gotten muddier.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "some", "ways", ",", "I", "think", "Mark", "is", "right", "that", "it", "has", "gotten", "muddier", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "It's an absolute basket case there, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "an", "absolute", "basket", "case", "there", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "EX", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "And it is heartbreaking.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "it", "is", "heartbreaking", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alan"]}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "The Arab Spring fallout, what is your take on that?", "question_tokens": ["The", "Arab", "Spring", "fallout", ",", "what", "is", "your", "take", "on", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "Well, I think I would like to go back to Alan's point, which is exactly right.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "I", "would", "like", "to", "go", "back", "to", "Alan", "'s", "point", ",", "which", "is", "exactly", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Arab Spring"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Hi, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Hi", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "Can we expect anything to improve?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "expect", "anything", "to", "improve", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Well, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "They wouldn't lie to us, would they?", "question_tokens": ["They", "would", "n't", "lie", "to", "us", ",", "would", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "I suppose the ones with the real problems are not the Democrats, because they've got back in.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "suppose", "the", "ones", "with", "the", "real", "problems", "are", "not", "the", "Democrats", ",", "because", "they", "'ve", "got", "back", "in", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "What do the Republicans do to try and reinvent themselves and make themselves more relevant, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "the", "Republicans", "do", "to", "try", "and", "reinvent", "themselves", "and", "make", "themselves", "more", "relevant", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "Well, I think they need to change their ideas rather than their people.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "they", "need", "to", "change", "their", "ideas", "rather", "than", "their", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "And what do you want him to do now that he has four more years?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "do", "you", "want", "him", "to", "do", "now", "that", "he", "has", "four", "more", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "The big thing he has going for him is that he has four years that he doesn't have to worry about getting re-elected.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "big", "thing", "he", "has", "going", "for", "him", "is", "that", "he", "has", "four", "years", "that", "he", "does", "n't", "have", "to", "worry", "about", "getting", "re-elected", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "Obama"]}, "docId": "121116pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "Where do you think he's been weak and where does he need to be stronger?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "been", "weak", "and", "where", "does", "he", "need", "to", "be", "stronger", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "Well, I think he's been weak -- my son was a huge Obama supporter until Obama ordered that American's death with the drone.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "been", "weak", "--", "my", "son", "was", "a", "huge", "Obama", "supporter", "until", "Obama", "ordered", "that", "American", "'s", "death", "with", "the", "drone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]